Guide to the Hans Reichenbach Papers, 1884-1972 ASP.1973.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Correspondence, Drawings, Manuscripts, Notebooks, and Photographs, 1884-1952; III.
  - Correspondence, Manuscripts, and Notebooks, 1903-1951; 3.
    - Atom und Kosmos (diagrams) (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Probability (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1934 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Probability Notes (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Time Additions (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Time Book: Detailed Notes (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Probability Notes, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Diagrams (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Entwürfe ("Philosophische Probleme der Relativitätstheorie.") (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Philosophische Notizen, 1912 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Kritische Axiomatik der Einsteinschen Zeitlehre (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, Manuscripts, and Notebooks, 1909-1920; 4.
    - Die Militarisierung der deutschen Jugend, 1911-1912 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Thesis: First Chapter (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Thesis: Partial (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence/Program der Ingenieur-Akadademie, 1915 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Letters from HR's parents and siblings to him, 1913 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Traffic Accident, 1909 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Über Elektronenröhren, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Patent-Sachen (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Patent Reports and Notes (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Notebook, 1920 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Graphics/Zur Theorie der Verstärkerröhren (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Notes on Electronics (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Rückkopplungsfreie Sender-Schaltung (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Axiomatik der Relativitäts-Theorie (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Notes on "Relativitäts-Theorie" (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence/Notes on Funkentelegraphisten (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Probability, Space & Time, Logic, 1924-1951; 5.
    - Konkurs: Karl Henschel, 1928-1930 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Zeitschrift Vorverhandlungen, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Mario Fax (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Begriff der Wahrscheinlichkeit (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Zur Raum-Zeit-Lehre (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Zur Axiomatik der Relativitätstheorie (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Philosophie der Raum-Zeit-Lehre (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Wahrscheinlichkeitslehre - Einzelheiten, 1948 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Notizen zur Wahrscheinlichkeit, 1935 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Theory of Probability - Hutton MS, Mia MS (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Notes on Direction of Time Used for MS (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Diagram for E.S.L. (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Time Chapter I - Plan (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Time Notes, 1951 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - WN-Function for Probability Transfer (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Time - Summaries (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Time MS (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Time Notes (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Vorträge - Institute Poincare, Mai - Juni, 1937 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Vorträge, 1924-1933 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Youthful Notes (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Paranoiker, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Tagung fur Erkenntnislehre, 1930 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Tagung fur Erkenntnislehre, 1929 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Manuscripts, Reprints, Radio, 1929-1947; 6.
    - Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Die physikalischen Voraussetzungen der Wahrscheinlichkeits-Rechnung, Manuscript (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Der Begriff des A-priori, Manuscripts (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Die Philosophische Bedeutung der Relativitäts-Theorie, Manuscript (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Of Truth and Error (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Reprints (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Radio (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Articles, 1929-1947 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Biography (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Manuskripte (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Manuskripte (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Manuskripte (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Manuskripte (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Reviews by Reichenbach and of His Work, Manuscripts, Lectures Notes, 1922-1964; 7.
    - Reviews of Reichenbach's Works, 1923-1925 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Reviews of Reichenbach's Works, 1931 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Mostly German Reviews of H.R.'s Books, 1929-1935 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Reviews of Books by H.R. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Reviews of Book by H.R., 1924-1926 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Reviews of Books by H.R., 1931 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Reviews of Erkenntnis (Journal edited by H.R.), 1931 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Reviews of Books by H.R., 1929 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Reviews of Books by H.R., 1939 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Philosophie der Naturerkenntnis, Manuscript, 1923 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Das physikalische Weltbild der Gegenwart, Manuscript, 1928 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Philosophie der Wahrscheinlichkeit, Manuscript, 1927-1930 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Geschichte der Philosophie, 1926 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Geschichte der neueren Philosophie, 1925 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Einführung in die Philosophie, 1925-1926 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Naturphilosophie (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Geschichte der neuren Philosophie, 1934-1935 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Kant und die moderne Naturwissenschaft, 1932-1933 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Logik - Notes (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Naturphilosophische Denker, 1928-1930 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Applied Logic, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Logik und Erkenntnistheorie, 1924-1925 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - Logik der exakten Wissenschaften, 1930-1935 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Physikalische Messungen, 1922-1923 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Lectures and Notes for Courses at UCLA, 1939 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Raum and Zeit (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Carnap Interview, 1939-1964 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Tests for Courses at UCLA (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Freedom of Will - Original Manuscript, 1952-1953 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Logic Tests (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Notebooks, Photos, and Correspondence, 1903-1924; 8.
    - Einstein Lectures Notebooks, 1918 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Alte Colleghefte: Berlin, Göttingen, Stuttgart, 1912-1924 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Alte Colleghefte: Berlin and Stuttgart, 1910-1923 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence between Reichenbach and Paul Hertz, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - School Notebooks, 1907 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - School Notebooks, 1903-1915 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Sketches and Drawings (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Photographs, Mostly from Time in US incl. Russell Family (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Typescript and Letter by Paul Hertz, 1921 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Logic, Notebooks, Family Correspondence, Radio Lectures, 1903-1939; 9.
    - Nomological Statements & Admissible Operations, Copy 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Nomological Statements & Admissible Operations, Copy 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Der Aufstieg der wissenschaftlichen Philosophie, by Hans Reichenbach, Translation to German by Maria Reichenbach,Typescript, Part I (Box 29, Folder 3a)
    - Der Aufstieg der wissenschaftlichen Philosophie, by Hans Reichenbach, Translation to German by Maria Reichenbach,Typescript, Part II (Box 29, Folder 3b)
    - Relative Nomological Implications in Revised Form, Manuscript (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Logical Analysis of Quantum Mechanics, Typescript (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Logical Analysis of Quantum Mechanics, Typescript (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Radio-Jugendstunde Berlin, Correspondence, 1927-1933 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Pirani, Marcello, Correspondence and Notes, 1920-1922 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Familienbriefe, Family Correspondence, 1912-1913 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Etwas vom Impfen (Zeitungsausschnitte/Article Clippings), 1909 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Small Notebook, 1913 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Early Notebooks (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Early Notebooks (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Jugendstunde, 1923-1925 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Radio-Vorträge von Mai 1929 bis Januar 1933 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - Manuskripte (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Radio-Vorträge Januar 27 - Oktober 28 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Arbeiter-Dialoge, 1931 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Notes to "Denken und Anschauung", 1929-1930 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Radio Notes (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - Postcards, 1929 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Manuscripts and Drafts, 10.
    - Experience & Prediction: Drafts, Chapter I (Box 30, Folder 40a)
    - Experience & Prediction: Drafts, Chapters II & III (Box 30, Folder 40b)
    - Experience & Prediction: Drafts, Chapter IV (Box 30, Folder 41a)
    - Experience & Prediction: Drafts, Chapter V (Box 30, Folder 41b)
    - Article Clippings, 1925 (Box 30, Folder 42a)
    - Photographische Ratschläge, Typescript (Box 30, Folder 42b)
    - Manuscripts Stuttgart: Willensfreiheit? Ein Dialog, by T. Lehor (Box 30, Folder 42c)
    - Manuscripts Stuttgart: Untitled (Box 30, Folder 42d)
    - Manuscripts Stuttgart: Die Probleme der modernen Physik (Box 30, Folder 42e)
    - Manuscripts Stuttgart: Relativity in the Matchbox. A Dialogue, English and German Versions (Box 30, Folder 42f)
    - Manuscripts Stuttgart: Die relativistische Zeitlehre (Box 30, Folder 42g)
    - Manuscripts Stuttgart: Die philosophische Bedeutung der Relativitätstheorie (Box 30, Folder 42h)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy, Drafts of the German Edition (Box 30, Folder 43a)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy, Drafts of the German Edition (Box 30, Folder 43b)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy, Drafts of the German Edition (Box 30, Folder 43c)
    - Corrections for the German Translation of Direction of Time (Die Richtung der Zeit), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Corrections for the German Translation of Direction of Time (Die Richtung der Zeit), 1977 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Die Richtung der Zeit, Kapitel I: Einführung (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Die Richtung der Zeit, Kapitel I: Einführung, Part II (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Die Richtung der Zeit, Kapitel I: Einführung, Part III (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - "La direción du temps," Manuscript by Maria Reichenbach (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "Space-Time", 1927 and 1956 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - "Space & Time," Part II (Box 31, Folder 8a)
    - "Space & Time," Part III (Box 31, Folder 8b)
    - "Space & Time," Part IV (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Probability Notes (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy: Images and Graphics (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy: Index (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy, Manuscript (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy, Retyped Pages (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy, Part I: The Roots of Speculative Philosophy (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Manuscripts, Articles, and Correspondence, 1920 and 1952-1971; 11.
    - Changes and Corrections to Various Manuscripts (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Carnap Memorial Meeting: Letters, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 2a)
    - Carnap Memorial Meeting: Letters, 1969-1971 (Box 32, Folder 2b)
    - Manuscripts (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Les fondements logique de la mecanique des quanta, Lectures Poincaré, June 1952 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Kolleg Relativitätstheorie, Stuttgart, Wintersemester, Part I, 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 5a)
    - Kolleg Relativitätstheorie, Stuttgart, Wintersemester, Part II, 1920-1921 (Box 32, Folder 5b)
    - Kolleg Relativitätstheorie und Erkenntnisbegriff, Kabellose Telegrafie, 1920-1922 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Entwürfe - Kausalität Stuttgart: Kausalrelation ohne Zeitbegriff (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Philosophical Foundations of Quantum Mechanics, Excerpts (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Philosophical Foundations of Quantum Mechanics, Part 1, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 9a)
    - Philosophical Foundations of Quantum Mechanics, Part 2, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 9b)
    - Philosophical Foundations of Quantum Mechanics, Part 3, 1943 (Box 32, Folder 9c)
    - Philosophical Foundations of Quantum Mechanics, Excerpt (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Outlines of the Mathematics of Quantum Mechanics, Part 1 (Box 32, Folder 11a)
    - Outlines of the Mathematics of Quantum Mechanics, Part 2 (Box 32, Folder 11b)
  - Reviews of Hans Reichenbach's Publications, 1924-1973; 12.
    - The Theory of Probability: Reviews, 1950-1972 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Philosophical Foundations of Quantum Mechanics: Reviews, 1944-1967 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Modern Philosophy of Science: Reviews, 1959-1963 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Philosophical Foundations of Quantum Mechanics: Reviews, 1945-1952 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Nomological Statements and Admissable Operations: Reviews, 1954-1959 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Direction of Time / Rise of Scientific Philosophy: Reviews, 1956-1973 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Axiomatik der relativistischen Raum-Zeit-Lehre: Reviews, 1966-1972 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Hans Reichenbach Bibliography / Elements of Symbolic Logic: Reviews and Correspondence, 1949-1962 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Bibliographies of Hans Reichenbach's Works, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - The Theory of Relativity and A Priori Knowledge: Reviews and Announcements, 1965-1967 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy: Letters and Reviews, Part I, 1951-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11a)
    - The Rise of Scientific Philosophy: Letters and Reviews, Part II, 1951-1969 (Box 36, Folder 11b)
    - Reviews: The Rise of Scientific Philosophy and Others, 1924-1953 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Reichenbach's Funeral: In Memoriam, Clippings, 1953 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Letters ("Fan Mail"), 1924-1964 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Letters and Announcements, 1936-1968 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Reviews and Articles, 1924-1962 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence with Publishers, 1937-1969; 13.
    - Applications, 1951-1954 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - A Letters, 1938-1967 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - B Letters, 1954 (Box 37, Folder 3a)
    - B Letters, 1952-1953 (Box 37, Folder 3b)
    - B Letters, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 3c)
    - B Letters, 1949-1950 (Box 37, Folder 3d)
    - B Letters, 1947-1948 (Box 37, Folder 3e)
    - B Letters, 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 3f)
    - B Letters, 1942-1943 (Box 37, Folder 3g)
    - B Letters, 1937-1939 (Box 37, Folder 3h)
    - B Letters, 1946-1953 (Box 37, Folder 3i)
    - Chicago University Press, 1938-1954 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - C Letters, 1938-1952 (Box 37, Folder 5a)
    - C Letters, 1938-1963 (Box 37, Folder 5b)
    - University of California Press, 1949-1964 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - University of California Press, 1951-1952 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - University of California Press, 1951 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - University of California Press, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - University of California Press, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - University of California Press, 1948 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - University of California Press, 1947 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - University of California Press, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - University of California Press, 1943-1945 (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - University of California Press, 1941-1942 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous, 1965-1967 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Carnap Letters, 1938-1952 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - D Letters, 1939-1962 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Dover, 1946-1965 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Einstein Estate, 1967 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - E Letters, 1943-1968 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - F Letters, 1939-1966 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Feigl Letters, 1951-1953 (Box 37, Folder 23a)
    - Feigl Letters, 1949-1953 (Box 37, Folder 23b)
    - Feigl Letters, 1951-1967 (Box 37, Folder 23c)
    - Feigl Letters, 1949-1951 (Box 37, Folder 23d)
    - Feigl Letters, 1947-1949 (Box 37, Folder 23e)
    - Feigl Letters, 1942-1968 (Box 37, Folder 23f)
    - G Letters, 1957-1974 (Box 37, Folder 24a)
    - G Letters, 1941-1953 (Box 37, Folder 24b)
    - G Letters, 1949-1956 (Box 37, Folder 24c)
    - G Letters, 1938-1953 (Box 37, Folder 24d)
    - G Letters, 1956-1968 (Box 37, Folder 24e)
    - H Letters, 1939-1953 (Box 37, Folder 25a)
    - H Letters, 1939-1951 (Box 37, Folder 25b)
    - H Letters, 1939-1953 (Box 37, Folder 25c)
    - H Letters, 1940-1953 (Box 37, Folder 25d)
    - H Letters (Box 37, Folder 25e)
    - H Letters, 1956-1965 (Box 37, Folder 25f)
    - H Letters, 1952-1966 (Box 37, Folder 26)
    - I Letters, 1938-1958 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - J Letters, 1938-1951 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - K Letters, 1937-1951 (Box 37, Folder 29a)
    - K Letters, 1937-1953 (Box 37, Folder 29b)
    - K Letters, 1939-1947 (Box 37, Folder 29c)
    - K Letters, 1949-1968 (Box 37, Folder 29d)
    - König Letters, 1965-1969 (Box 37, Folder 29e)
    - Landé Letters, 1952-1954 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - L Letters, 1948-1955 (Box 37, Folder 31a)
    - L Letters, 1939-1952 (Box 37, Folder 31b)
    - L Letters, 1939-1951 (Box 37, Folder 31c)
    - L Letters, 1939-1952 (Box 37, Folder 31d)
    - L Letters, 1941-1967 (Box 37, Folder 31e)
    - Mac Letters, 1941-1966 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Macmillan, 1946-1963 (Box 37, Folder 33a)
    - Macmillan, 1939-1948 (Box 37, Folder 33b)
    - Macmillan, 1946 (Box 37, Folder 33c)
    - Macmillan, 1945-1946 (Box 37, Folder 33d)
    - Macmillan, 1944-1945 (Box 37, Folder 33e)
    - Macmillan, 1939-1963 (Box 37, Folder 33f)
    - M Letters, 1948-1969 (Box 37, Folder 34a)
    - M Letters, 1940-1958 (Box 37, Folder 34b)
    - M Letters, 1944-1958 (Box 37, Folder 34c)
    - M Letters, 1943-1958 (Box 37, Folder 34d)
    - M Letters, 1939-1967 (Box 37, Folder 34e)
    - N Letters, 1937-1965 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - O Letters, 1941-1952 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - P Letters, 1938-1963 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Philosophic Abstracts Library & Philosophic Library, 1941-1965 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Q Letters, 1949-1953 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Russell Letters, 1963-1967 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Routledge & Kegan Paul, 1956-1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - R Letters, 1939-1965 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Strauss Letters, 1938-1946 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Sch Letters, 1939-1951 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - S Letters, 1940-1968 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - T Letters, 1942-1967 (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - University of California, 1952-1964 (Box 38, Folder 13a)
    - University of California, 1944-1952 (Box 38, Folder 13b)
    - University of California, 1939-1946 (Box 38, Folder 13c)
    - University of California, 1937-1939 (Box 38, Folder 13d)
    - University of California, 1952-1968 (Box 38, Folder 13e)
    - U Letters, 1951-1958 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - V Letters, 1945-1968 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - W Letters, 1938-1967 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Z Letters, 1938-1968 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Lectures, Drafts, and Publications, 1926-1957; 14.
    - Difference Between Deduction and Induction (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Statistical Mechanics, 1943-1944, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - On the Freedom of Will (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Inductive Consistency, 1952 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - The Latest Works of Reichenbach, The Emotive Significance of Time, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Theory of Relativity and A Priori Knowledge, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Probability Notes (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Probability Problems, 1940-1950 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Binomial Coefficients and Bose-Fermi Statistics, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Logik Behariorismin Carnap ve Reicenbacha Göre Tefsiri, 1938 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Entwürfe zur Quanten-Mechanik, 1926-1932 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Responses to Questionnaire by Maria Reichenbach for Selections of The Selected Papers of Hans Reichenbach] including Correspondence, 1953-1955 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Manuscripts Istanbul, 1935-1937 (Box 39, Folder 13a)
    - Manuscripts Istanbul Part II, 1935 (Box 39, Folder 13b)
    - Lectures in French given by H.R. in Istanbul (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Lectures/Vorträge Istanbul, 1932-1938 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - Papers Given by Mia at Various Meetings, 1942-1960 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - Maria Reichenbach Lectures, 1949-1965 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Explication of Ethical Utterances: Can Operators Reach Through Quotes?, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - "Existence of Classes," "On Meaning," "Indexical Signs," "Ethical Utterances," Papers, 1939, 1952-1953 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Bohm Paper (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Three Articles from Erkenntnis, Translation by Bruce Taylor, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Three Articles from Erkenntnis trans. by Bruce Taylor, 1932 (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Philosophy of Space & Time - Index (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Logic, Lectures, Publishers, 1937-1953; 15.
    - Laws and Counterfactuals, Manuscript, 1953 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Outlines of Lectures, 1944-1948 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Indexical and Token-Reflexive Signs, unpublished MS, 1939-1953 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Handwritten MS (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Ø and the Implications of Science, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Quantum Mechanics, Manuscript, 1931-1948 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Quantum Mechanics, Manuscript, 1941-1944 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Direction of Time, Manuscript, 1941-1949 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Hilbert's E-System, Elementary Solution of the Problem of 4 Colors (Bernoulli's Theorem), Notes, 1939-1947 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Problems in Probability, 1937-1943 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Induction for Bernuolli Sequence (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Probability MIM Problems, 1940-1944 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Problems for Advanced Logic (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Course Material, 1943-1952 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - French Lectures on Axiomatics and Paradox (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Notizen, 1932-1938 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Linguistic Notes (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Book List Ordered for the University Library in Istanbul (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Mathematical Formulas, Photograph of Tomb, 1937-1949 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Wahrscheinlichkeitsbriefe, 1924-1936 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Experience and Prediction, 1937-1938 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Induction, 1937-1949 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Logic Notes, 1939-1950 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Miscellany - Unidentified, 1946-1953 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Notes on Time Book, 1942-1953 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Philosophy and Science, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 26)
    - Drawings for Time (Box 40, Folder 27)
    - Diagrams, The Direction of Time (Box 40, Folder 28)
    - Diagrams and Footnotes for The Direction of Time (Box 40, Folder 29)
    - Reply to Hempel (Box 40, Folder 30)
    - Bohm Paper (Box 40, Folder 31)
    - Bohm Paper with Correspondence, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Notes and Correspondence, 1891-1978; 16.
    - Corrections to Various Works by H.R. (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Seminar Papers by Graduate Students at UCLA, 1931-1952 (Box 41, Folder 2a)
    - Seminar Papers by Graduate Students at UCLA, 1953 (Box 41, Folder 2b)
    - Bibliography and Mailing List by H.R. (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Reidel Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Picture of H.R. for Scientific American, 1958 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - University of California, 1935, 1946 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Notebooks by HR, 1891-1917 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Hans Reichenbach - Elizabeth, 1915-1917 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Certificates/Diplomas, 1906-1924 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1911-1934 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Hans Reichenbach Official Documents, 1894-1933 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1914-1938 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Reidel Plan for The Vienna Circle Collection, 1970-1973 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Introduction to Reidel's Moral Scientific and Philosophical Views (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Maria Reichenbach - Elizabeth, 1974-1975 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Maria Reichenbach - Others, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Maria Reichenbach - Others, 1973-1977 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Socializing the University (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Maria Reichenbach - Salmon, Wesley, 1970-1978 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - The Syllogism Revised, 1952, 1973 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Weyl's Extension of the Riemannian Concept of Space, Appendix (Box 41, Folder 21)